Guide to the Stanford University, Board of Trustees, Safe Deposit Box Documents SC0766
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Board of Trustees, safe deposit box documents
1860-1948
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Board of Trustees
SC0766
1.5 Linear Feet
Assorted documents once kept in a bank safe deposit box including copy of the Founding Grant, 1885; Petition by Leland Stanford Junior University and of individual trustees for the ascertainment of the existence and terms of, and for the determination of the validity and legal effect of grants or other instruments, creating, changing or affecting trusts and estates for the founding, endowment, and maintenance of the Leland Stanford Junior University, 1906; certified copy of minutes of the Board of Trustees contained in Volume One for November 14, 1885 and August 29, 1903 to April 30, 1904; inventory and appraisal of the estate of Leland Stanford, 1893; Organization of the Board of Trustees, Nov. 1, 1901; and U. S. Patent of Esquon Ranch to Samuel Neal (Butte County, Calif.), with plat map, dated April 3, 1860.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Assorted documents once kept in a bank safe deposit box including copy of the Founding Grant, 1885; Petition by Leland Stanford Junior University and of individual trustees for the ascertainment of the existence and terms of, and for the determination of the validity and legal effect of grants or other instruments, creating, changing or affecting trusts and estates for the founding, endowment, and maintenance of the Leland Stanford Junior University, 1906; certified copy of minutes of the Board of Trustees contained in Volume One for November 14, 1885 and August 29, 1903 to April 30, 1904; inventory and appraisal of the estate of Leland Stanford, 1893; Organization of the Board of Trustees, Nov. 1, 1901; and U. S. Patent of Esquon Ranch to Samuel Neal (Butte County, Calif.), with plat map, dated April 3, 1860.
Land grants.; Stanford, Leland; Stanford, Jane Lathrop; Stanford University. Board of Trustees; Stanford University. Board of Trustees; Neal, Samuel.
- Safe Deposit Box Documents
  - Compared Copy of the Founding Grant, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Petition by Leland Stanford Junior University and of individual trustees for the ascertainment of the existence and terms of, and for the determination of the validity and legal effect of grants or other instruments, creating, changing or affecting trusts and estates for the founding, endowment, and maintenance of the Leland Stanford Junior University, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Certified copy of minutes of the Board of Trustees contained in Volume One for, Nov 14, 1885, Aug 29, 1903-Apr 30, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Inventory and appraisal of the estate of Leland Stanford, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Receipt to Jane Lathrop Stanford from Samuel F. Leib, 1901 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Petition...for determination of validity..., 1906 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Organization of the Board of Trustees, 1901-11-01 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Receipt of the Wells Fargo...bonds..., 1919-09-04 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Patent of Esquon Ranch to Samuel Neal (Butte County, Calif.), with plat map, April 3, 1860 (Box 2, Folder 6)